afajof.org 2016-03-15

# - American Finance Association

John Wiley & Sons, Ltd recognise the importance of protecting the information collected from website users in the operation of this website, and take reasonable steps to maintain the security, integrity and privacy of any information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. By submitting your information to the Website you consent to the practices described herein.

We will seek to ensure that any identifiable personal information it collects during the registration and purchasing processes will be adequate, relevant and not excessive for purposes of operating this website or any of the services operated hereunder and it will be kept accurate and up-to-date based on information provided. Except as expressly provided herein or, unless we have received your consent, we will not disclose any personal information identifying users to any third party except where necessary in connection with services provided by appropriate intermediaries, who will be required to comply with the confidentiality provisions of this policy. In addition, we may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties in order to comply with the law or requests by law enforcement agencies, to enforce our [Terms and Conditions ](http://www.afajof.org/terms.html)or to protect the rights, property or safety of our website, content, users or others. In the event that all or substantially all of the business or assets relating to this website are sold or otherwise assigned to another entity, personally identifiable information may be transferred to such entity. Personal information and any other communications or information supplied to us may be used for internal business and research purposes and to help enhance and develop our products and websites.  

If you provide us with your address, you may receive periodic catalogues or other notices containing information about new products and services or upcoming events. On occasion, we may make our mailing address lists available to other companies who we believe may have products and services of interest to our customers. If you do not wish to receive mailings from us or our partners, please let us know via phone, fax, mail, or email (See [Contact Us](http://www.afajof.org/contact.html)). Please provide us with your exact name and address and state which lists you wish to be removed from so that we can be sure your information is removed from those mailing lists. If use of an electronic product, feature or service offered on this website requires a user to provide a name and password or other personally identifiable information, the user will have the option to opt in or out of providing such information and using the product, feature or service.  

We may disclose to carefully chosen third parties navigational and transactional information in the form of anonymous, aggregate usage statistics (including "page views" on this website and the products herein) and demographics but only in forms that do not reveal a user's identity or confidential information, except as required by law, as needed in connection with legal proceedings, or unless we have received your consent. Cookies are small text files placed on your computer by websites you visit. Cookies may be used to remember information about your activities on the website and enable the operator of the site to customize your experience or to monitor usage of the website for analysis. An overview of the types of cookies we use on this website and information about how cookies can be deleted or disabled can be found at [About Cookies.](http://eu.wiley.com/WileyCDA/Section/id-817085.html)

Links may be provided from this website to other third party websites. In using such links, users should be aware that each third party website is subject to its own privacy and data protection policies and is not covered by our privacy. In addition, we allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may be placing and reading cookies on your computer's hard disk or using web beacons or other technologies to collect information in the course of ads being served on this website. More information can be found at [About Cookies](http://eu.wiley.com/WileyCDA/Section/id-817085.html). To opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)or follow the instructions for opting out provided in the third party ad servers' privacy and data protection policies. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy and data protection policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not take responsibility for the privacy policies of, and usage of, personal information collected by others, including without limitation, those of any partner or affiliate.

You should be aware that identifiable personal information--such as your name or e-mail address--that you voluntarily disclose that is accessible to other users (e.g. on bulletin boards or in chat areas) could be collected and disclosed by others. We cannot take any responsibility for such collection and disclosure. In addition, we may share information you voluntarily provide in response to an advertisement with the third party serving the advertisement.

Please note that this Privacy Policy is reviewed periodically. We reserve the right to modify its Privacy Policy at any time without notice. Any changes to the policy will be posted on this page. Your continued use of this website will be deemed conclusive acceptance of such modification. Any comments or questions concerning this policy should be addressed by entering your comments through our [Contact Us ](http://www.afajof.org/contact.html)page. If at any point you wish to access your personal information to (1) change your preferences, (2) review the accuracy, or (3) correct, supplement or modify your information, please Contact Us in writing to John Wiley & Sons Ltd, The Atrium, Southern Gate, Chichester, West Sussex , PO19 8SQ, England. If you wish to modify your shopping account, you can do it directly in the My Account section.
